[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "type": "text",
    "question": "巻雲 の略称は何ですか？",
    "answer": "Ci",
    "explanation": "巻雲 (Ci)"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "type": "text",
    "question": "巻積雲 の略称は何ですか？",
    "answer": "Cc",
    "explanation": "巻積雲 (Cc)"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "type": "text",
    "question": "巻層雲 の略称は何ですか？",
    "answer": "Cs",
    "explanation": "巻層雲 (Cs)"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "type": "text",
    "question": "高積雲 の略称は何ですか？",
    "answer": "Ac",
    "explanation": "高積雲 (Ac)"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "type": "text",
    "question": "高層雲 の略称は何ですか？",
    "answer": "As",
    "explanation": "高層雲 (As)"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "type": "text",
    "question": "乱層雲 の略称は何ですか？",
    "answer": "Ns",
    "explanation": "乱層雲 (Ns)"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "type": "text",
    "question": "層積雲 の略称は何ですか？",
    "answer": "Sc",
    "explanation": "層積雲 (Sc)"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "type": "text",
    "question": "層雲 の略称は何ですか？",
    "answer": "St",
    "explanation": "層雲 (St)"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "type": "text",
    "question": "積雲 の略称は何ですか？",
    "answer": "Cu",
    "explanation": "積雲 (Cu)"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "type": "text",
    "question": "積乱雲 の略称は何ですか？",
    "answer": "Cb",
    "explanation": "積乱雲 (Cb)"
  }
]